cellzddl.com 2009-04-15

# PRIVACY | Free Mobile Games

**PRIVACY POLICY**  
Cellzddl.com, respects the privacy rights of our online visitors, and subscribers and members of our web site www.Cellzddl.com (the ”Site”) and is committed to protecting the personal information collected about you. To further this commitment, we have adopted this Privacy Policy (”Privacy Policy”) to guide how we collect, store, and use the information you provide us. By visiting our Site, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use. For our information collection and use practices with respect to children under 13, please see our special children’s section below.

**I. SCOPE OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY**  
This Privacy Policy applies only to information submitted and collected online through the Site, and does not apply to information that may be collected by Cellzddl offline.  
By using and submitting personal information, you signify your assent to this Privacy Policy. Cellzddl reserves the right, at any time and without notice, to add to, change, update or modify this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, simply by posting such change, update or modification on the Site. Any such change, update or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on the Site. Your continued use of any of our websites will signify your acceptance of these changes.

**II. INFORMATION COLLECTED**  
Personal Information  
To access certain services offered via the Site, Cellzddl may collect information about you, but only if you voluntarily provide it to us.  
The types of personal information collected in conjunction with the activities listed above will vary depending on the activity. The requested information may include: (i) your name, (ii) mailing address, (iii) telephone number, (iv) email address, and, for those purchasing products online, (v) credit card information. Parents or legal guardians providing parental consent (via our Parental Consent Form) may be asked to provide their child’s name and email address in addition to information about themselves. You may choose not to provide certain information, but in doing so you may not be able to take advantage of many of our features.  
Use of Cookies  
Cellzddl may use cookies on its Site. A “cookie” is a small bit of record-keeping information that sites often store on a user’s computer. Cookies do not include people’s names, email addresses, or other information that is personally identifiable; they are typically used to quickly identify a user’s computer and to “remember” things about the user’s visit. You can disable cookies or set your browser to alert you when cookies are being sent to your computer, although this may affect your ability to shop online and login.

**III. USE OF INFORMATION COLLECTED**  
Cellzddl may use your Personal Information to send you information about our company or our features, products or services, or promotional material from some of our partners, or to contact you when necessary, unless the customer has disagreed that Cellzddl uses its data.  
Cellzddl also may use your Personal Information for editorial and feedback purposes, for marketing and promotional purposes, for a statistical analysis of users’ behavior, for product development, for content improvement, and to customize content and layout of the Site. Names, postal and e-mail addresses and phone numbers collected may be added to our databases and used for future calls and mailings regarding site updates, new products and services, upcoming events and the status of orders placed online. If you no longer wish to receive promotions or other offers, please click here: http://www.Cellzddl.com/optout.  
Cellzddl does not sell or rent your Personal Information to third-parties for marketing purposes without your consent. Cellzddl may share your Personal Information you provide with Cellzddl subsidiaries and related companies. Cellzddl may share Personal Information with business partners that assist Cellzddl in providing you services. Cellzddl is committed to giving you the choice whether or not Cellzddl uses your information for marketing purposes or shares information with business partners.

**IV. COLLECTION AND USE OF CHILDREN’S PERSONAL INFORMATION**  
The Site complies with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (”COPPA”). Cellzddl does not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13 through the Site. In addition, in the event that a user identifies himself or herself as a child under the age of 13 within the Site or in connection with any Content or Software, Cellzddl will not collect, store or use any personal information of such user. Further, in the event that Cellzddl receives personal information that Cellzddl discovers was provided by a child under the age of 13, Cellzddl will promptly delete such personal information in a secure manner.

**V. SAFEGUARDS**  
Cellzddl maintains appropriate safeguards that ensure the security, integrity, and privacy of the personal information we collect and store about our account holders, including children under 13. Personal information collected by Cellzddl is stored in secure operating environments that are not available to the public and that are only accessible by authorized employees. In addition, our online store uses industry-standard encryption to prevent unauthorized electronic access to sensitive financial information such as your credit card number. We also have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control (i.e., maintain data quality). Before we allow web users to access their personal information, for example, we verify their identity by requesting that they submit information such as their username and password. We also take reasonable steps to ensure that third parties to whom we transfer personal information provide sufficient protection of such data.

**VI. LINKS TO THIRD PARTY SITES**  
You should be aware that the Site may from time to time contain links to third-party web sites. Cellzddl is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites. If you are concerned about the privacy policy of a certain third party, we recommend that you read the privacy policy of the website to which you link before you submit any personal information.

**VII. ACCESS TO MY PERSONAL INFORMATION**  
To review, update, or correct Personal Information, you may first login using your username and password. Then, by clicking on the Edit Profile button on the navigation bar, you can access and change your account information. If you want us to remove your Personal Information from our list or would like to access information that was collected, please contact us using the contact information provided below:  
If you have any questions, complaints, or comments regarding this Privacy Policy or our information collection practices, please contact us at : cellzddlservice@gmail.com

Cellzddl [Mobile Games](http://www.cellzddl.com/)&[Mobile Themes  
](http://www.cellzddl.com/)
